<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<creature>
  <info id="720000">

    <narration action="move">
      #0 enters $0's containment unit to begin work.
    </narration>

  </info>

  <observe level ="4">
    <collection>
      <codeNo openLevel ="0">O-09-314</codeNo>

      <portrait openLevel ="1">Custom/th</portrait>

      <name openLevel ="1">
        Judgement of Shamash
      </name>

      <riskLevel openLevel ="1">WAW</riskLevel>

      <openText>I made a promise to her, to everyone, that no matter what the cost, humanity would triumph over the Collapse!</openText>

    </collection>

   <desc id="1" openLevel="0">
      [
      {The Abnormality was discovered in a meteorite after the company deciphered
the name of the Abnormality and discovered that it came from a world that had collapsed.
It is the Key of Destruction, made from the core of the Seventh Ruler of the ancient world,
It is a twin-gun weapon that possesses great destructive power born from the power of "heat"}
      ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="2" openLevel="1">
      [
      {It has a black and white barrel, while the Ruler's core is crimson.
The core has a safety mechanism in place. To limit its power, the core of the Ruler
was split into two pieces and placed in the twin guns.
It isn't very powerful, as this mechanism caused the twin gun barrels to
stretch and morph to form the hilts of the sword, and a hot flame, like molten gold, rises up to the sky and coalesces into the sword's body.}
      ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="3" openLevel="2">
      [
      {The method of use is called the Sheath of Heavenly Fire, and as the name suggests,
it brings absolute destruction to all things.
The storm of flames created by the Great Sword is capable of destroying even the most powerful of creatures,
but this power comes at a heavy price, as those who dare use it are burned to ashes when unleashing the Sheath of Heavenly Fire.}
      ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="4" openLevel="3">
      [
      {When the weapon has reached its full power, it will remove the safety
and transform into a devestatingly powerful weapon. 
It could be considered an incarnation of death itself, and only the light that erupts from a supernova could compete with it.
This is the origin of the name "Kabuto". Only one who can surpass the limits of mortality can withstand it.}
      ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="5" openLevel="4">
      [
      {By the time the company deciphered all information about it, they found a single sentance visable on the scorched earth where the meteor fell:
I made a promise to her, to everyone, that no matter what the cost, humanity would triumph over the Collapse!}
      ]
    </desc>


    <specialTipSize size="5">
      <specialTip openLevel="1" key="1">This Abnormality contains great power. It can be wielded by employees.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="2" key="2">It causes those who use it to lose HP in order to deal exponentially increased damage.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="3" key="3">When it is used twice by the same employee in a single day, they will die a strange and unprescedented death.</specialTip>
    </specialTipSize>
  </observe>
</creature>