<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<creature>
  <!--
    info - 관찰 레벨과는 관련 없는 정보들 ex)데미지, id, 이미지 소스 등

    observe - 관찰 정도에 따라 제공되는 정보들
              각 정보들에는 정보가 제공되는 레벨을 표기
              ex) <desc id="1" openLevel="1">"openLevel이 1일 때 이 정보가 제공됨"</desc>

              observe 노드 안의 level 은 관찰 단계의 갯수를 나타냄
  -->
  <info id ="165880">



    <narration action="move">
      #0 enters $0's containment unit to begin work.
    </narration>

    <narration action="mid1">
      [
      {Stench emanates from $0.}
      ]
    </narration>
    <narration action="mid2">
      [
      {#0 feels sick.},
      {There is a constant flow of filth flowing from $0.}

      ]
    </narration>
    <narration action="mid3">
      [
      {The smell can cause weaker willed individuals to throw up on the spot.}
      ]
    </narration>
    <narration action="mid4">
      [
      {$0 doesn't just spew out filth, you know.}
      ]
    </narration>

  </info>

  <observe level ="1">
    <collection>
      <codeNo openLevel ="0">O-02-21-11</codeNo>
      <portrait openLevel ="1">Custom/AmblingPearl</portrait>

      <name openLevel ="1">
        Ambling Pearl
      </name>

      <riskLevel openLevel ="1">
        WAW
      </riskLevel>

      <openText>That shell... that damned shell...!
What comes out of there....</openText>

    </collection>

    <desc id="1" openLevel="0">
      [
      {Record 1: O-02-21-11
Recorder: Colored Staff

~Start Recording~.

Colored Staff: Work order to O-02-21-11... I'm on my way.

~Colored staff member enters the housing room and attempts to start work~.

Colored Staff: Ugh...I think I'm going to throw up...it stinks like hell.... Let's finish the work as soon as possible...

～Colored Staff proceeds with the work...

Colored Staff: Why does it smell so... bad...? Is the substance coming out of there bad?

～Colored Staff vomits...

Colored Staff: That's not just a bunch of filth! That's... there's a lot of ■■ in that ■■■■■!}
      ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="2" openLevel="1">
      [
      {Record 2: O-02-21-11

From Record 1, we found the cause of the foul odor from the O-02-21-11 housing unit.
It is caused by the substance being produced from O-02-21-11.
That was....I don't want to record any more of this.
If you are going to work on O-02-21-11, please work with personnel of high mental capacity.}
      ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="3" openLevel="2">
      [
      {Note: We have done additional research on the produced substance.
Substances seem to increase or decrease depending on the results of the work.
However, as much as possible, please keep the amount of produced substance level, because if the amount of substances increases or decreases too much, the Abnormality will grow volitile.}
      ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="4" openLevel="3">
      [
      {Record 3: O-02-21-11
Recorder: Ten Staffer

The following is a record of the escape of O-02-21-11

Announcement: O-02-21-11 has escaped. The instructed personnel should proceed to suppress O-02-21-11.

Ten Staffer: Damn! Why is that smell so potent? I'm not even at O-02-21-11 yet!

～Ten Staffer looks around~

Ten Staffer: What is it? Wait... This green slime... is this the cause of the stench? We can't focus with this stuff around, so lets destroy it on the way!

～Just as the Ten Staffer is about to destroy the substance, O-02-21-11 entered the area.}
      ]
    </desc>
    <desc id="5" openLevel="4">
      [
      {Ten Staffer: What? Is it trying to eat this stuff? That can't be good... I'd better destroy it before it gets the chance.

～Ten Staffer interupts the Abnormality, and is successful in destroying the substance.

Ten Staffer: Ugh, this things surprisingly nimble... Eh? What's happening now?

～At the same time, the same substance was confirmed to have been destroyed at another location.

Ten Staffer: It popped open... Well, its easier to hit like this. I guess I'll aim for that shining pearl there.

~ Successful suppression of O-02-21-11 ~.

Based on the above record, if O-02-21-11 has escaped, destroy the material that appeared, and if O-02-21-11 has opened, aim for the pearl.
Note: Do not allow O-02-21-11 to take in the substance.}
      ]
    </desc>



  <specialTipSize size="6">
      <specialTip openLevel="1" key="1">At the beginning of the day, $0 owned 5 green mucus.
$0 could acquire up to 20 green mucus.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="2" key="2">At the end of the work, the staff member who was doing the work received WHITE damage.
Also, if the work result was good, the Qliphoth Counter decreased and $0 gained 3 green mucus.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="3" key="3">If the work result was bad, the Qliphoth Counter increased and $0 lost 3 green mucus.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="4" key="4">When the green mucus count reached 10 or more, or was lowered to 0, $0's Qliphoth Counter lowered to 0.
During the breakout, $0 fixed the amount of green mucus it possesed to 10, and three green slime appeared in the facility.
The green slime took vastly increased damage when attacked by $0.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="5" key="5">If a green slime was defeated by a staff member, $0's green mucus count was reduced by 3. If $0 was suppressed by a staff member, $0's green mucus was increased by 3.
Also, when a green slime was destroyed, a new green slime appeared somewhere in the facility.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="6" key="6">During the escape, if $0's green mucus was reduced to 0, $0 stopped moving and $0's resistances were greatly weakened.
However, after 30 seconds had passed in this state, $0 gained 10 green mucus and its resistances were restored.</specialTip>
   </specialTipSize>

  </observe>

  <child>
    <name>Green Slime</name>
    <codeId>O-02-21-11</codeId>
  </child>

</creature>