<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<creature>
  <!--
    info - 관찰 레벨과는 관련 없는 정보들 ex)데미지, id, 이미지 소스 등
    
    observe - 관찰 정도에 따라 제공되는 정보들
              각 정보들에는 정보가 제공되는 레벨을 표기
              ex) <desc id="1" openLevel="1">"openLevel이 1일 때 이 정보가 제공됨"</desc>
              
              observe 노드 안의 level 은 관찰 단계의 갯수를 나타냄
  -->
  <info id ="110012">



    <narration action="move">
      #0 enters the Containment Unit of $0.
    </narration>

    <narration action="mid1">
      [
      {#0 feels as if their body is drained of energy.}
      ]
    </narration>
    <narration action="mid2">
      [
      {$0's woes are unfathomably deep.},
      {$0 wishes for their grief to be absolved.},

      ]
    </narration>
    <narration action="mid3">
      [
      {#0 feels pain, as if their head and chest were being crushed.}
      ]
    </narration>

  </info>

  <observe level ="1">
    <collection>
      <codeNo openLevel ="0">F-05-33</codeNo>
      <portrait openLevel ="1">Custom/DrownedSister</portrait>

      <name openLevel ="1">
       The Drowned Sisters
      </name>

      <riskLevel openLevel ="1">
        HE
      </riskLevel>

      <specialName openLevel ="1">
       Sorrow
      </specialName>
      <openText>"Why did you despise us so?"</openText>
    
    </collection>

    <desc id="1" openLevel="0">
      [
      {Why did you despise us so? Why did you bear so much hatred that you wished for our demise?}
      ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="2" openLevel="1">
      [
      {Had you spoken a single word, had you spoken that you loathed us so much...}
      ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="3" openLevel="2">
      [
      {Ahh, woe is us. We have become sinners. Please hear us, hear of our sins that we do not know we've committed...}
      ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="4" openLevel="3">
      [
      {Absolve us of our grief...}
      ]
    </desc>


    
  <specialTipSize size="5">
      <specialTip openLevel="0" key="nope">When an employee finished work with another Abnormality, $0's Qilphoth counter decreased.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="0" key="nope">When the Insight work result was good, its Qliphoth counter increased.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="0" key="nope">Upon finishing Repression work, the Qliphoth counter dropped to 0.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="0" key="nope">When the Qliphoth Counter reached 0, the hallway the Abnormality was in flooded with water. Employees attempting to traverse the flooded hallway was dealt heavy WHITE damage.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="0" key="nope">Listening to $0's woes through Absolve work set $0's Qliphoth counter back to full. However, Prudence of the employee who undertook the work was halved for the rest of the day.</specialTip>
     </specialTipSize>
    
    <max>
      <!--기본 선택지-->
      <desc id="0" select="1">
        [
        {The stage was set a long time ago, and here's a man who caused many to die.}
        {Coincidentally, you have a gun.}
        <!--계속-->
        ]
      </desc>

      <!--선택지-->
      <select id="1">
        <node desc="Shoot him." target="1" isAnswer="true"  message="The curtains open." />
        <node desc="Watch." target="2" isAnswer="true" message="The curtains open." />
        <node desc="Shoot someone else." target="3" isAnswer="true" message="The curtains open." />
      </select>

      <desc id="1" select="0">
        [
        {You decide to shoot the man.}
        {Finally, the curtain falls.}
        ]
      </desc>

      <desc id="2" select="0">
        [
        {The barrel of the gun lost its aim.}
        {The stage ends in a tragedy.}
        ]
      </desc>

      <desc id="3" select="0">
        [
        {The stage ends in a comedy.}
        ]
      </desc>

      <!--스토리 파트에서 출력될 부분-->
      <angela>
        [
        {"A sinner spectating a play, moved by its eccentric ways of expressing things confesses their sins on the spot. A play is sure to reveal the true scheme underneath."}
        ]
      </angela>
    </max>
    
  </observe>

  <etc>
    <param key="attack1" index="0"> <!-- 더미데이터였던...카핰 -->
      A : (Narrating) He was but a self-centered, arrogant character. (Stroking mask) I knew so from the start. Disaster follows disaster.
    </param>
    <param key="attack2" index="1">
      A : (Narrating) One abadoned by the world, I shall serve with death, for I am qualified so. A thirst yet to be quenched approaches.
    </param>
    <param key="attack3" index="2">
      A : (Narrating) His despair had already seeped deep within his bones, eating at him from the inside out. Though he was always smiling, he loathed himself on the inside.
    </param>
    <param key="attack4" index="3">
      A: (Narrating) He is but a coward, avoiding his own failures. I cannot forgive him. I'm one who strolls through Heaven or Hell on my own accord with you!
    </param>

    <param key="kill1" index="4"> <!-- 각각 죽이고 나서 대사 으안안ㅁ아앜앜어안ㄴ앜 -->
      (The one who failed falls)
    </param>
    <param key="kill2" index="5">
      (The one who was abandoned falls)
    </param>
    <param key="kill3" index="6">
      (The one who despaired falls)
    </param>
    <param key="kill4" index="7">
      (The one who avoided it all falls)
    </param>


    <param key="finale1" index="8"> <!-- 쥔공한테 총 쏠때-->
     A :  To die is to fall into slumber, nothing else. (Falls)
    </param>

    <param key="finale2" index="9"><!--총 안쏠때-->
      A : Were sins revealed in my dialogue? (The lights go out)
    </param>

    <param key="finale3" index="10"> <!-- 다른 사람한테 쏠때-->
      A :  Lord above, no. Help me. Please, deliver me from this pain. (Crushing silence)
    </param>
    
    

    <param key="special" index="11"> <!-- 특수공격 발동 되기 시작할때-->
      You are now incapable of controlling Agent #0. All his focus is on that book. The stageplay starts.
    </param>


    <param key="end" index="12"> <!-- 연출없이 끝날때-->
      You, lost in the dark and surrounded by silence. Though dawn used to break, it's now but an eternal night. If I could reach you, I would lead you out of this sickening darkness into the radiant light.
    </param>




  </etc>
  

</creature>