<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<creature>
  <info id="29003">

    <narration action="move">
      #0 enters $0's containment unit to begin work.
    </narration>

  </info>

  <observe level ="4">
    <collection>
      <codeNo openLevel ="0">O-09-326</codeNo>

      <portrait openLevel ="1">Custom/CallFromThePostDeathWorld</portrait>

      <name openLevel ="1">
        A Phone Call from Hell
      </name>

      <riskLevel openLevel ="1">TETH</riskLevel>

      <openText>Place the receiver to your ear, and you will hear voices from another world.</openText>

    </collection>

    <desc id="1" openLevel="0">
      [
      {An obsolete old landline telephone. It has laid abandoned for many years, causing the white shell to somewhat yellow.
Investigation revealed that a large number of parts were missing, and the internal wiring had been ripped apart.}
      ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="2" openLevel="1">
      [
      {Whenever someone passes nearby, a hollow ringing sound will come from the phone.
Investigation into the origins of the phone have not produced results on its origins. Some speculate that it operates on magic.
Place the receiver to your ear, and you will hear voices from another world.}
      ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="3" openLevel="2">
      [
      {What happens after we die? I couldn't stop thinking about it, after I heard about my coworker's suicide.
It took a few days for people to find his body, but oddly enough, his face was still identifiable.
I still remember his smiling expression. I wonder if he saw a glimpse of what happens after death.
I wonder if it was beautiful.}
      ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="4" openLevel="3">
      [
      {I heard a rumor that this phone connected to the afterlife. I don't know if it's true, but...
Trembling and lifting the receiver, I dialed the phone number of that colleague. After a moment, someone responded.
“Don't...! Don't come to this horrible place...!”
Amidst the mournful screams, I heard my coworker's heartbreaking voice.
A few seconds later, the other end of the phone fell silent.}
      ]
    </desc>

    <specialTipSize size="4">
      <specialTip openLevel="1" key="1">Employees who answer the phone will continuously lose SP.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="2" key="2">When an employee is answering $0, all employees in the department
will gain work success rate and work speed over time. 
They will also recover a small amount of HP at intervals.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="3" key="3">Employees who stay on the line for too long will be dragged to hell.</specialTip>
    </specialTipSize>
  </observe>
</creature>