<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<localize>
<text id="sanchez_weapon_name">&lt;color=#A45864&gt;Look across the Lethe&lt;/color&gt;</text>
  <text id="sanchez_weapon_specialDesc">&lt;color=#5A9D8B&gt;When an attack hits an enemy, it grants a RED resistance debuff. When attacking, there is a 20% chance of using a special attack.&#13;&#10;If 'River of Contrition' is equipped, heal HP for 30% of the damage inflicted when attacking.&lt;/color&gt;</text>
<text id="sanchez_weapon_desc">A weapon extracted from the river Styx.&#13;&#10;An eternal cyan flame seems to encase the whole scythe.&#13;&#10;By simply cutting one's flesh, can the soul be easily taken.&#13;&#10;Only employees who're fearless of death can utilize this weapnon.&#13;&#10;&lt;color=#A45864&gt;I glared at the forgotten depths, I gazed to the abyssal lethe. The stone of Samsara moves, the lily of Faramita blossoms. I fell prisoner to this endless river, I gave birth to those countless annoyances... &lt;/color&gt;</text>
<text id="sanchez_armor_name">&lt;color=#A45864&gt;Imprisoned River&lt;/color&gt;</text>
  <text id="sanchez_armor_specialDesc">&lt;color=#5A9D8B&gt;Employees equipped with this armor will regain their HP and SP once a day when their SP falls below 20%.&#13;&#10;Once the effect is triggered, the employee deals increased damage for the rest of the day.&lt;/color&gt;</text>
<text id="sanchez_armor_desc">A suit extracted from the river Styx.&#13;&#10;An eternal cyan flame seems to encase the whole scythe.&#13;&#10;Employees wearing this E.G.O will be more sensitive to the voices of souls.&#13;&#10;&lt;color=#A45864&gt;Why are you imprisoned at the river, what do you seek from the river?  To end the dream from the previous life, to cut the karma from the present cycle. The lethe has flowed for countless decades, but the mind and soul shall never fade...&lt;/color&gt;</text>
<text id="sanchez_gift_name">&lt;color=#A45864&gt;Never Returning&lt;/color&gt;</text>
<text id="sanchez_gift_Desc">&lt;color=#5A9D8B&gt;HP+7 SP+3 Movement Speed+5 Attack Speed+5&lt;/color&gt; &#13;&#10;&lt;color=#A45864&gt;It is merely a dream. Now, return home.&lt;/color&gt;</text>
<text id="villa_weapon_name">&lt;color=#5682BB&gt;Broken Wings&lt;/color&gt;</text>
  <text id="villa_weapon_specialDesc">&lt;color=#FDD47E&gt;When an attack hits an enemy, it grants a PALE resistance debuff. When attacking, there is a 20% chance of using a special attack.&#13;&#10;Employees equipped with this weapon will have their damage vary according to their SP.&lt;/color&gt;</text>
  //&#13;&#10;Increase damage by 5 when SP is above 80%.&#13;&#10;Increase damage by 3 when SP is between 50%～80%.&#13;&#10;Increase damage by 1 when SP is between 20%～50%.&#13;&#10;Decrease damage by 5 when SP is below 20%. 
<text id="villa_weapon_desc">This weapon was given to three good-related birds.&#13;&#10;The quill is so bright and colorful, that is seems like it has an actual soul.&#13;&#10;The possessor of this quill will attach more attention to their comrades.&#13;&#10;And only those who are courageous and responsible could freely wield it.&#13;&#10;&lt;color=#5682BB&gt;The rainbow colors were reflected by scarlet feathers, the misty sky was carried upon azure wings.&lt;/color&gt;</text>
<text id="villa_armor_name">&lt;color=#5682BB&gt;Hundred Birds&lt;/color&gt;</text>
<text id="villa_armor_specialDesc">&lt;color=#FDD47E&gt;Employees equipped with this armor will recover 20 SP to each employee in the same room as them every 10 seconds.&#13;&#10;The overflow recovery is converted into a WHITE shield.&#13;&#10;Employees who have their SP healed have their Fortitude and Justice stats increased by 3 for 50 seconds.&lt;/color&gt;</text>
<text id="villa_armor_desc">This suit was extracted from the hundreds of birds in the woods.&#13;&#10;Light and soft feathers were sewn all over this suit, making it appears like it doesn't belong to the mortal world. &#13;&#10;The wearer of this E.G.O can regain courage when stuck in a dilemma.&#13;&#10;&lt;color=#5682BB&gt;Jade clouds were penetrated by nimble feathers, Strong wind was broken by elegant wings.&lt;/color&gt;</text>
<text id="villa_gift_name">&lt;color=#5682BB&gt;Never Fear&lt;/color&gt;</text>
<text id="villa_gift_Desc">&lt;color=#FDD47E&gt;SP+10 Success Rate+5 Work Speed+5&lt;/color&gt; &#13;&#10;&lt;color=#5682BB&gt;Through the light rain, swallows fly past, Burning the red feather, crimson smoke emits.&lt;/color&gt;</text>
<text id="bella_weapon_name">&lt;color=#B48662&gt;Sinking sand&lt;/color&gt;</text>  
<text id="bella_weapon_specialDesc">&lt;color=#8F9F54&gt;When an attack hits an enemy, it grants a WHITE resistance debuff. When attacking, there is a 20% chance of using a special attack.&#13;&#10;Each enemy hit by attacks will be slowed down, and if their RED resistance is not greater than 0, they will take BLACK damage instead.&lt;/color&gt;</text>
<text id="bella_weapon_desc">A weapon grown from the desert.&#13;&#10;The roots growing on this broadsword might be the only force holding back the all-devouring sand.&#13;&#10;Those who came in contact with the tip of this blade will find themselves with dull mind and reduced movements.&#13;&#10;Employees must have a precise distinction of friend and foe before they could wield this weapon.&#13;&#10;&lt;color=#B48662&gt;Feather splitted and sunk into sand, once broad ocean now reduced to dry land. I lamented you who had left, gone and will never come back.&lt;/color&gt;</text>
<text id="bella_armor_name">&lt;color=#B48662&gt;Pear Shaded&lt;/color&gt;</text>
<text id="bella_armor_specialDesc">&lt;color=#8F9F54&gt;Employees wearing this armor will receive damage reduction in proportion to lost HP.&#13;&#10;While equipped with 'Sinking Down', special attacks grant a BLACK shield to employees in the same area.&lt;/color&gt;</text>
//20% damage reduction when HP is above 50%, 50% damage reduction when HP is between 20%～50%, 70% damage reduction when HP is below 20%. 
<text id="bella_armor_desc">A suit grown from the desert.&#13;&#10;This suit is filled with pulsating life, it might offer protection to those who're not accustomed to this dehydrated environment.&#13;&#10;The wearer of this E.G.O gains a "tree shade" with protective capabilities.&#13;&#10;&lt;color=#B48662&gt;Smal,l green leaves formed a shield for life, Lively, lush branches created a garden of past.&lt;/color&gt;</text>
 <text id="bella_gift_name">&lt;color=#B48662&gt;Never Leaving&lt;/color&gt;</text>
<text id="bella_gift_Desc">&lt;color=#8F9F54&gt;HP+10 Success Rate-2 Work Speed+7 Movement Speed+5 &lt;/color&gt;&#13;&#10;&lt;color=#B48662&gt;Leaning resting against the tree, we laughed and sang in the scattered rain, lying drunk over the sand, we watched the stars spreading all over the sky.&lt;/color&gt;</text>
<text id="voidream_gift_name">&lt;color=#A45482&gt;Engulfing Dream?&lt;/color&gt;</text>
<text id="voidream_gift_Desc">&lt;color=#A486BB&gt;SP+4 &lt;/color&gt; &#13;&#10;&lt;color=#A45482&gt;A specific employee's strong desire for dreams caused the enlargement of this E.G.O gift.&lt;/color&gt;</text>
<text id="svb_gift_name">&lt;color=#977E7C&gt;Unregretting&lt;/color&gt;</text>
<text id="svb_gift_Desc">&lt;color=#8F9F54&gt;HP+12 &lt;/color&gt; &lt;color=#FDD47E&gt;SP+5 &lt;/color&gt; &lt;color=#5A9D8B&gt;Movement Speed+7 Attack Speed+7 &lt;/color&gt; &#13;&#10;&lt;color=#A45864&gt;If the employee equipped both "Look across the Lethe" and "Imprisoned River" when they possess this gift, heal SP by 30% of the damage when their SP was damaged.&lt;/color&gt;&#13;&#10;&lt;color=#5682BB&gt;If the employee equipped both "Broken Wings" and "Hundred Birds" when they possess this gift, aside from the aforementioned effects, heal HP by 15% of the damage when their SP was damaged.&lt;/color&gt;&#13;&#10;&lt;color=#B48662&gt;If the employee equipped both "Sinking sand" and "Pear Shaded" when they possess this gift, deal 5 extra BLACK damage with each attack.&lt;/color&gt;&#13;&#10;&lt;color=#977E7C&gt;If the employee have equipped "Never Returning", "Never Fearing" and "Never Leaving" at the same time, once every day, ignore fatal damage and gain a shield instead.&#13;&#10;I have no other regrets in my life, for I've met friends like you. &lt;/color&gt; </text>
<text id="picky_gift_name">Picky's Nose？？</text>
<text id="picky_gift_Desc">SP+4 &#13;&#10;What? Where did this gift come from?</text>
<text id="picky_armor_name">Hamster Wheel</text>  <text id="picky_armor_desc">A pajama with unknown origins.&#13;&#10;It is very comfortable and fluffy by the touch, but whoever wears this outfit will appear extra chubby.&#13;&#10;And the wearer might attempt to feed desserts made from unidentified ingredients to their coworkers.&#13;&#10;Gosh, which backstreet inhabitant will wear this!</text>
<text id="picky_armor_specialDesc">Every 10 seconds, it restores 10 HP and deals 5 SP damage to other personnel in the same area.&#13;&#10;While wielding 'Back to Basics', restores 15 HP and 5 SP instead of the above effects. </text>
<text id="picky_weapon_name">Rich Fat Salt</text>
<text id="picky_weapon_desc">Bacon made from unknown meat.&#13;&#10;emits a tempting, oily fragrance, and will gradually become shorter in battle...&#13;&#10;The only thing is, it's a bit too salty! It might give its target a......salty death? &#13;&#10;This little fellow is so gluttonous!</text>
<text id="picky_weapon_specialDesc">During suppressions, the weilder attempts to consume bacon, regaining HP and reducing the range and power of the weapon.&#13;&#10;After dealing 30 damage, deal 30 SP damage to the target as well.&#13;&#10;Employees carrying this piece of bacon will destroy corpses they walk over, regaining their bacon.</text>
</localize>