<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<creature>
  <!--
    info - 관찰 레벨과는 관련 없는 정보들 ex)데미지, id, 이미지 소스 등
    
    observe - 관찰 정도에 따라 제공되는 정보들
              각 정보들에는 정보가 제공되는 레벨을 표기
              ex) <desc id="1" openLevel="1">"openLevel이 1일 때 이 정보가 제공됨"</desc>
              
              observe 노드 안의 level 은 관찰 단계의 갯수를 나타냄
  -->
  <info id ="316011">



    <narration action="move">
      #0 Staff enters the $0 room to begin work.
    </narration>

    <narration action="mid1">
      [
      {Starting from a doubt born one day, I ultimately fell to this place.},
      ]
    </narration>
    <narration action="mid2">
      [
      {To understand the origin and meaning of $0, numerous processes of unraveling their history are required.},
      ]
    </narration>
    <narration action="mid3">
      [
      {Even if $0 could see where they were meant to reach far ahead, they chose to crawl on the ground.},
      ]
    </narration>
    <narration action="mid4">
      [
      {At the end of the helix, will there truly be an answer?},
      ]
    </narration>

  </info>

  <observe level ="1">
    <collection>
      <codeNo openLevel ="0">O-05-98</codeNo>
      <portrait openLevel ="1">Custom/AnswerOfMachines</portrait>

      <name openLevel ="1">
        Answer
      </name>
      <name openLevel ="3">
        The Dead Answer
      </name>

      <riskLevel openLevel ="1">
        WAW
      </riskLevel>

      <openText>To protect the 'answer' they had reached, they clad themselves in heavy armor.</openText>

    </collection>

    <desc id="1" openLevel="0">
      [
      {We were wandering in search of an answer.}
      ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="2" openLevel="1">
      [
      {At one point, some of us discovered a suspicious equation. 
      It was a clue that might lead us to an answer.}
      ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="3" openLevel="2">
      [
      {We spent time solving that equation.
      And finally, we reached it...the answer.}
      ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="4" openLevel="3">
      [
      {After a while, we came to realize that the 'answer' we had sought was not what we truly should have been searching for. We were deeply disheartened.
       Leaving behind those who clung to the 'answer', we decided to abandon it.}
      ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="5" openLevel="4">
      [
      {=================}
      ]
    </desc>  

    <desc id="6" openLevel="4">
      [
      {To protect the 'answer', that person clad themselves in heavy armor.  The more they reinforced their defenses, the less they were able to move.}
      ]
    </desc>



    <specialTipSize size="1">
      <specialTip openLevel="0" key="0">When the work results were poor, the Qliphoth Counter decreased.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="1" key="1">When the work results were good, the Qliphoth Counter increased with a very low probability.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="2" key="2">Each time a specific ordeal occurred, the Qliphoth Counter decreased.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="3" key="3">During $0's escape, $0 occasionally used a cannon connected to &lt;Redacted&gt;. The cannon was extremely lethal, and employees targeted by it often died in many cases. However, employees with high physical abilities or those who took specific actions had a relatively higher survival rate.</specialTip>
    </specialTipSize>
  </observe>
</creature>