<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<creature>
  <info id ="156514">
    <narration action="move">
      #0 enters the Containment Unit of $0.
    </narration>

    <narration action="mid1">
      [
      {$0 is a massive slab of stone with a base made of red muscular fibers},
      ]
    </narration>
    <narration action="mid2">
      [
      {The bricks of $0 start creaking},
      ]
    </narration>
    <narration action="mid3">
      [
      {The bricks of $0 are engraved with letters from ancient languages},
      ]
    </narration>

  </info>

  <observe level ="1">
    <collection>
      <codeNo openLevel ="0">M-04-04-05</codeNo>
      <portrait openLevel ="1">Custom/DoomsdayCalendar_portrait</portrait>

      <name openLevel ="1">
        Doomsday Calendar
      </name>

      <riskLevel openLevel ="1">
        HE
      </riskLevel>

      <openText>You, too, will be a live offering.</openText>

    </collection>

    <desc id="1" openLevel="0">
      [
      {Placed on a wooden pedestal that seemed as though it was woven from fibers of muscles was a large stone slab}
      ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="2" openLevel="1">
      [
      {When agents approach it, its compartments of bricks began to rattle. Seized by curiosity, the agents attempt to get closer for a better observation.
}
      ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="3" openLevel="2">
      [
      {Based on the numerous letters carved on the bricks, it is highly likely that it is a tool used for predicting a certain date. The letters come from an ancient language, and that slab is almost certainly a calendar.}
      ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="4" openLevel="3">
      [
      {"I had an opportunity to be offered to this. I took unwavering steps forward as the choice was reasonable."

}
      ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="5" openLevel="3">
      [
      {"I had no reason to fear, for I would be brought back to life even if I were to perish.
I did not feel the death, so to speak. Though I have experienced death many times in battle, I was not subjected to the sort of pain or flashing disarray that normally accompanies a demise that time. It simply felt as though I was being transported to a different location.
It may be the universe or some other dimension."}
      ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="6" openLevel="4">
      [
      {"My own body and voice couldn't be perceived by my senses. Perhaps my eyes had gone and I became a part of that place.
There, I may have seen the end. You could say it was a doomsday I witnessed.
No perhaps I may have been the end and the doomsday I was present at the end but not existent and while it may be misleading to say that it was there but even still I witnessed man and sky and earth tear into thousands of pieces"}
      ]
    </desc>



    <specialTipSize size="6">
      <specialTip openLevel="0" key="0">The Qliphoth Counter of $0 will decrease by 1 at the start of meltdown level.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="1" key="1">After performing the sacrifice work on $0, its Qliphoth Counter will immediately increase, causing certain damage to the agent or clerk involved.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="2" key="2">The lower the Qliphoth Counter, the higher the damage caused by the sacrifice work.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="4" key="4">After the Qliphoth Counter of $0 reaches zero, it will enter a state of countdown for 120 seconds and only perform Sacrifice work will be avaliable. If the counter remains at zero for a whole 120 seconds, it will inflict high black damage on units within a certain range.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="3" key="3">Once the counter reaches 0, it will generate 3 "Doomsday Clay Doll" every 60 seconds and also reduce its own counter further.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="5" key="5">When a "Doomsday Clay Doll" dies, it will immediately increase the Qliphoth Counter of $0, however 60 seconds have to pass before you can increase the counter again killing a clay doll, this counter raise temporarily delays the massive black wave of damage.</specialTip>
    </specialTipSize>
  </observe>

  <child>
    <name>Doomsday Clay Doll</name>
    <codeId>M-04-04-05-A</codeId>
  </child>
</creature>