<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<localize>
  <text id="RCorp4thPackA">All of you, stand at attention.</text>
  <text id="RCorp4thPackB">Hey now, I thought my rabbits and I were the only ones in the pack being sent? Why are those two loudmouths here?</text>
  <text id="RCorp4thPackC">My rabbits were doing fine on their own!</text>
  <text id="RCorp4thPackD">Silence, Myo. L Corp. asked for more variety in the troops sent to them, so we're providing it.</text>
  <text id="RCorp4thPackE2">With the addition of newly discovered Abnormalities, it was decided that a means of subdueing them besides the rabbits was needed.</text>
  <text id="RCorp4thPackF2">So you're calling on rhinos that can't do anything but smash, and reindeer that go insane and attack their allies? The rabbits should be enough.</text>
  <text id="RCorp4thPackG2">You're worried about your fragile rabbits being abandoned, which is understandable, since you'be been bragging about being deployed to L Corp. so much.</text>
  <text id="RCorp4thPackH2">I'm just telling you the truth. I don't want another team to screw up and jeopardize our contract with L Corp.</text>
  <text id="RCorp4thPackI2">I thought the useless rabbits were doing their job properly, but since we're being involved now, are you worried you're being discarded?</text>
  <text id="RCorp4thPackJ2">Don't worry, we're still working on the contract together.</text>
  <text id="RCorp4thPackK2">What'd you say, you one-antler reindeer?</text>
  <text id="RCorp4thPackL2">I said, useless rabbits.</text>
  <text id="RCorp4thPackM2">Both of you, shut up. If you continue to argue in public, I'll cull the both of you myself.</text>
  <text id="RCorp4thPackN2">Apologies, sir.</text>
  <text id="RCorp4thPackE">Meh~</text>
  <text id="RCorp4thPackF">By the way, is this the headquarters of L Corp? I gotta say, I'm not impressed.</text>
  <text id="RCorp4thPackG">I mean, look, the manager of this wing is so scrawny! If the rhinos were to wreak havoc here, there's no way they'd survive.</text>
  <text id="RCorp4thPackH">When I said 'Shut up', I was including you, Maxim.</text>
  <text id="RCorp4thPackI">S-Sorry, sir!</text>
  <text id="RCorp4thPackJ">Captain. While the rhino's behavior is problematic, I do agree with him.</text>
  <text id="RCorp4thPackK">The reason why only the rabbits were initially sent was due to the nature of the reindeer and rhino teams.</text>
  <text id="RCorp4thPackL">While I'm happy our contract is being renewed and expanded, if a problem arises due to our characteristics, it's possible that L Corp will hold us responsible.</text>
  <text id="RCorp4thPackM">I think that is something that we must address.</text>
  <text id="RCorp4thPackN">That's right! The rhino team isn't some lowly fixer group, you know.</text>
  <text id="RCorp4thPackO">If we went on a rampage, we can't be held responsible if we smash up a containment unit or two!</text>
  <text id="RCorp4thPackP">It'd be bad if we got sent a bill for damages, after all!</text>
  <text id="RCorp4thPackQ">Things were going fine with us rabbits. Now that we're adding the rhinos and reindeer, it's gonna cause a lot of problems. We'll probably lose a lot of rabbits.</text>
  <text id="RCorp4thPackR">Just to remind you, this sort of enviroment is ideal for the rabbits.</text>
  <text id="RCorp4thPackS">A clause was added in the contract that states that R Corp. is not responsible for any damages caused during work hours.</text>
  <text id="RCorp4thPackT">...Though, I would be remiss not to clairfy: You said that Lobotomy Corporation has made improvements regarding the characteristics of the rhinos and reindeer, but are you certain?</text>
  <text id="RCorp4thPackU">It could be a problem for us, so we need to get it right.</text>
  <text id="RCorp4thPackV">I examined the characteristics of the reindeer and rhino teams in the materials provided by R Corp.</text>
  <text id="RCorp4thPackW">The other teams were prohibited due to the damages the rhino team would cause to the facility, and the potential mental damage the reindeer could cause the manager.</text>
  <text id="RCorp4thPackX">However, as our facility has discovered and contained new Abnormalities, we realized that the rabbit team may not be sufficient to handle the new threats.</text>
  <text id="RCorp4thPackY">And so, the decision was made to renovate the facility and to bring on the rest of the 4th pack.</text>
  <text id="RCorp4thPackZ">To that end, I've enhanced the defenses of the Manager against the reindeer team's mental attacks to the point they won't harm the manager.</text>
  <text id="RCorp4thPacka">I've also reinforced the containment units of the Abnormalities to withstand the brunt of the rhino team.</text>
  <text id="RCorp4thPackb">Should any damages be caused despite this, no charge will be made against R Corp, just like with the rabbits.</text>
  <text id="RCorp4thPackc">Good. Now that we've determined that there are no issues, the reindeer and rhino will be dispatched. I will now recite the revised contract.</text>
  <text id="RCorp4thPackd">R Corp. will provide military support and protection from all external threats to L Corp.</text>
  <text id="RCorp4thPacke">Every branch of Lobotomy Corporation will be included under the term "L Corp", however there will be certain exceptions where a branch may not be considered under the designation.</text>
  <text id="RCorp4thPackf">Exceptions are incidents that involve the eyes and the head, and R Corp is not responsible for any problems that arise in these situations.</text>
  <text id="RCorp4thPackg">L Corp. will provide the energy R Corp. needs to maintain its operation.</text>
  <text id="RCorp4thPackh">L Corp. will provide all specialized ammunition utilized for the killing of Abnormalities.</text>
  <text id="RCorp4thPacki">R Corp. is not responsible for the destruction of facilities, killing of employees, and mental damage that occurs during operations.</text>
  <text id="RCorp4thPackj">All 4th Pack members will have their memories erased after the completion of their missions.</text>
  <text id="RCorp4thPackk">Finally, the captains of each team in the 4th pack will deploy their teams following R Corp's guidelines and assume the role of command for operations taking place in this facility.</text>
  <text id="RCorp4thPackl">The renewal period for the contract will be one year, as before.</text>
  <text id="RCorp4thPackm">One year for you guys, you mean!</text>
  <text id="RCorp4thPackn">Well, that's a rabbit's share of annoyance.</text>
  <text id="RCorp4thPacko">Right? It's always such a hassle.</text>
  <text id="RCorp4thPackp">Since you're putting the full force of the 4th pack into Lobotomy Corporation, we'll give ours in turn.</text>
  <text id="RCorp4thPackq">Lobotomy Corporation is giving us their full support: let's ensure they get their moneys worth.</text>
  <text id="RCorp4thPackr">The reindeer specialize in mental dominance, so we'll have a leg up on the other teams in that regard.</text>
  <text id="RCorp4thPacks">Be cautious: longer missions may risk the minds of the reindeer, and could cause us to go mad.</text>
  <text id="RCorp4thPackt">Leave the heavy lifting to the rhinos, they're strong and powerful enoguh to outlast the impractical reindeer and rabbits!</text>
  <text id="RCorp4thPacku">Be careful, though. When we get too excited, we'll go on a rampage!</text>
  <text id="RCorp4thPackv">Rabbits are the quickest and the most efficient, most of the time.</text>
  <text id="RCorp4thPackw">In general, you'll find that most common situations can be resolved with just the rabbits.</text>
  <text id="RCorp4thPackx">When all three teams are called upon, I'll personally take command. You may rely on my skill and efficacy in such matters.</text>
  <text id="RCorp4thPacky">However, be aware that we will need to charge a heavier fee for such situations.</text>
  <text id="RCorp4thPackz">Well, that's all then. Good day, Manager.</text>
</localize>