<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<creature>
  <info id ="819401">



    <narration action="move">
    </narration>
    <narration action="start">
      [
      {\}
      ]
    </narration>
    <narration action="mid1">
      [
      {\},
      ]
    </narration>
    <narration action="mid2">
      [
      {\},
      ]
    </narration>
    <narration action="mid3">
      [
      {\},
      ]
    </narration>
    <narration action="mid4">
      [
      {\},
      ]
    </narration>

  </info>

  <observe level ="1">
    <collection>
      <codeNo openLevel ="0">O-01-20-12</codeNo>
      <portrait openLevel ="1">Custom/SFZW-KoisCode-819401-portrait</portrait>

      <name openLevel ="1">
        The King in Binds
      </name>

      <riskLevel openLevel ="1">
        WAW
      </riskLevel>

      <openText>The banquet has concluded, but the king haven't had enough fun yet……</openText>

    </collection>

    <desc id="1" openLevel="0">
      [
      {An empty banquet hall, wreathed in ambient crimson light.

The solitary king, bound to his throne, raises his arm in an unhurried motion.

Your feet grow drenched in the cold mist of a vague tune.

The lone king gently points to a platform near you with an inviting cadence.

On it are masks, each depicting different spectrum of emotions.

There is a mask of joy. A mask of sorrow. A mask of wrath.

I know not the reason for which this mask embodies such expression of euphoria; yet, shan’t it be enough that it shall share the selfsame joy with others?

Two birds with one stone; solace shared, sorrow shrouded, the twain under a blanket of elation.

I wear the mask and feel my thoughts grow clear as an autumn sky.

Upon my approach, the king tensed his shoulders for a moment so brief that it was nigh unnoticed.

Perhaps it was a gesture borne not out of thought but of instinct, shaped by the cloth-suppressed will to express.

We had but a moment to regard it before those akin in appearance to us appeared.

Though their forms were opaque and their shapes half-shrouded in shadow, they held certain similitudes to our own forms.

The monarch, with certain torpidity, tipped his head to the side in a show of intent to behold our battle.

The long years spent in binds have filled the void left behind by your long-gone interests with tedium, have they not?

A terribly tragic tale. Yet we battle in hopes that our clashes may bring this king in binds the smallest revelry.}
      ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="2" openLevel="1">
      [
      {What those Peccatula lack is the will to make decisions of their own.

Like cards to be played with and discarded at the king’s whim.

Kings, both of eld and new it seems, enjoy plays of puppets, a musical of manikins.

Wielding men as cold tools, brandishing and flourishing them with abandon, breaking them. And upon their inevitable shattering, the king shall fill their spot with another puppet, its absence unnoticed.

Yet, this king may be quite fond of his own.

To shower his retinue with ceaseless blessings while leaving naught for the rest of us.}
      ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="3" openLevel="2">
      [
      {Passion grows hotter as the banquet slowly reaches a crescendo.

The King in Binds motions for the battle to pause.

Giving the actors enough time to leave their broken masks and don new ones for themselves.}
      ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="4" openLevel="3">
      [
      {Donning the mask once again summons the ardent emotions that slowly simmer into the actors' hearts.

The sorrow rises through the fog of heated battle; its dense weight pierces deep, deep into their emotions.

Yet, the banquet continues still......

The actors repress their sorrows and step forward.}
      ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="5" openLevel="4">
      [
      {Thus concluded it seemed the banquet.

Yet the King's tedium was yet to be sated; the bound monarch rose from his throne, tearing free his corpus from the bandage-chains.

The long time spent in confinement has rusted his joints, yet his imposing presence and grace have only grown to touch the formidable grandeur of his sublimity.

His resolute resolve roused awe in the hearts of those who beheld his emergence.

Yet awe was not the only sense it roused; a question arose as well.

For what did the king remain tethered to his throne, when he had the might to rise on his own?

I… know not why the king remained in sedentary silence, bound not by the threads but by his own will.

I write a few words here still, for I cannot very well put to sleep the simmering ruminations…

It appears that the king has aught to convey.

A monarch fettered to this spot, ere the hail of those who may discern his fathoms. A wraithlike state the sovereign has taken.

This somber musing heaps and heaps with every blade-clash unto a mound of sorrow as sympathy falls sunken.

Whyever does he hold one such banquet, his corpus bound to the throne, only to revel in such bizarre festivity?

It is but a pitiful tragedy, for this abyss is deep and wreathed in inexplicability.}
      ]
    </desc>



    <specialTipSize size="7">
      <specialTip openLevel="0" key="0">$0 have a major difference compared to other Abnormalities, it was contained in the department main room instead of a containment unit. When in calm state, $0 will grant extra HP&amp;SP recovery to employees in the main room, and attack any enemy unit in the main room.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="1" key="1">When the employees are suppressing other enemies in the main room where $0 resides, $0 will grant shield for combatants on both sides, the side which deals more damage will be granted more shield.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="2" key="2">$0's emotion can be measured in the scale of "satisfaction", When the work result is good, "satisfaction" will increase; When the work result is bad, "satisfaction" will decrease; When $0 was attacked, "satisfaction" will significantly decrease. If Repression work was performed on $0, the employee performing the work will be instantly executed.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="3" key="3">Instinct work is replaced by Performance work. When Performance work begins, all employees located in the main room where $0 resides will become "actors", $0 will summon Peccatulum Inividiae equal to the number of the employees for them to combat.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="4" key="4">When Performance work was being performed, $0's "satisfaction" will gradually increase. If the Performance work took more than 30 seconds to complete, $0's "satisfaction" will further increase; If the Performance work took less than 20 seconds to complete, $0's "satisfaction" will decrease, if the actors quit during performance, $0's "satisfaction" will decrease significantly.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="5" key="5">When $0's "satisfaction" increases, all employees in the main room will recover HP&amp;SP; When $0's "satisfactioni" decreases, all employees in the main room will recieve BLACK damage. 上升时The greater the magnitude of "satisfaction" change, the stronger the recovery or damage.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="6" key="6">When $0's "satisfaction" is too low, $0 will enter enraged state, teleporting all employees of this department to the main room, then sealing the main room and begin a performance. $0's wrath can only be quenched when its "satisfaction" rises to a certain threshold or its HP was brought to 0.</specialTip>
    </specialTipSize>
  </observe>
  <child>
    <name>The King in Binds</name>
    <codeId>O-01-20-12</codeId>
  </child>
</creature>