<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<creature>

  <info id="101168">

    <narration action="move">
      #0 heads to “$0's" containment unit to begin work.
    </narration>

    <narration action="start">
      [
      {"$0" is essentially a regular corpse, except it is suspended in the air.}
      ]
    </narration>
    
    <narration action="mid1">
      [
      {#0 is about to vomit their breakfast because of the stench.}
      {#0 frets as the body in front of them explodes without warning.}
      ]
    </narration>
    
    <narration action="mid2">
      [
      {Goodnight, Mr. Whale.}
      {The stench of decay will grow stronger as the time goes on...}
      ]
    </narration>
    
    <narration action="dead">
      [
      {The pressure was too much for "$0" to take, and with a bang, the unit was strewn with rotten flesh.}
      ]
    </narration>
  </info>

  <observe level="4">
    <collection>
      <codeNo openLevel="0">T-01-168</codeNo>
      <portrait openLevel="1">Custom/FloatingWhale</portrait>

      <name openLevel="1">Floating Whale</name>
      
      <riskLevel openLevel="1">TETH</riskLevel>

      <openText>The kids claim to have seen a green whale on the beach...</openText>

    </collection>

    <desc id="1" openLevel="1">
      [
      {"Whale Explosion" is a rare natural phenomenon that typically occurs when a whale strands or dies. The combination of external air pressure and internal gas generated by decomposition causes the body to burst, creating a sudden explosion of flesh, blood, and organs.}
      ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="2" openLevel="2">
      [
      {...&#13;&#10;I don't think I'll ever go to that beach again.&#13;&#10;You likely know why. But allow me to explain.&#13;&#10;It was a sunny morning, I had gone to the beach with a couple of kids from the neighborhood, It was just us, and I thought we had everything we needed, "what could go  wrong?".&#13;&#10;We had a blast, really.&#13;&#10;As the only grown-up there, I had to take care of the children, so I chose to follow them and found a bunch of green whales motionless on the seaside... already lifeless.&#13;&#10;You're aware that it's normal for whales in such cases to burst, right? I quickly tried to move the youngsters away from the spot; I still can't forget the bad smell in the atmosphere when one of the whale corpses exploded unexpectedly.&#13;&#10;I did my best...}
      ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="3" openLevel="3">
      [
      {&lt;Excerpted data from an encyclopedia&gt;&#13;&#10;Whenever a person dies and the body is not embalmed within 5 to 8 days, it undergoes a high degree of decay. This process produces a large amount of putrid gases which fill the soft tissues throughout the body, resulting in severe swelling including an extremely swollen face and protruding eyeballs, thickened and turned out lips, stretched out tongue, abdominal expansion, green skin, subcutaneous tissue and muscle emphysema, thickening of the limbs, the entire body swollen into a giant, it becomes difficult to guess how it used to look in life, this phenomenon is known as the Liquefactive stage of decomposition.}
      ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="4" openLevel="4">
      [
      {Several children were taken from their homes by an unknown man.&#13;&#10;Their parents begged us to find them offering a generous reward, and our staff eventually discovered them in a contaminated pool at an industrial site. Most of the children were badly affected by radiation, and a few were confirmed dead. Not far from where the children were, we found many decomposing bodies in Liquefactive state. with a strange man.&#13;&#10;Later, an investigation revealed that the man suffered from intense paranoia. He used his description of the ocean to lure some children, who had never been exposed to the ocean, to a waste pool.&#13;&#10;We do not know what the parents of those children did to him. However, we found his body one week later.}
      ]
    </desc>

    <specialTipSize size="4">
      <specialTip openLevel="1" key="1">$0 Qliphoth counter decreased when the work result was bad.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="2" key="2">$0 generates significant amounts of energy during Repression work. However, if it is repressed again within the same day, its body will explode, resulting in severe Black damage to the employee working with it.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="2" key="3">After bursting, $0 will stabilize and will no longer be able to breach for the day, but its energy output will drop dramatically.</specialTip>
      <specialTip openLevel="3" key="4">The supression or bursting of $0 can trigger other abnormalities.</specialTip>
    </specialTipSize>

  </observe>

</creature>